Subscribe to Warn Channel Advent
500 rica
It's delicious just to know that our members made it!
I want to spend the rest of my life with these members as my life partner.
I said it at the Forsberman Live event.
This is what I really think!
How was our hospitality?
Thank you very much!
And now for the fun part!
What is it?
Let's play a wargame first.
You know most of the rules.
I'd like to learn the rules as we play.
We'll learn the rules as we play.
Yes, sir.
Don't let other people see you.
What? What?
Okay, first, fortune teller, open your eyes.
Next, knight, open your eyes.
Now, medium, open your eyes.
Now, werewolves, please open your eyes.
First, out of these nine, decide who will be the first to be banished.
Yes, sir.
I'm a citizen.
I'm a citizen too.
He's got something to say.
First of all, let's start with the fortune teller.
I'm a fortune teller. Our Fortune Teller
Uh huh...
Wait a minute. When you said you were a citizen...
Amu, me, Yajima Yuna and Koe came forward!
There's definitely a wrong number of people.
I was thinking of inviting someone like this into the house... once.
One person for now.
They're all fortune tellers.
Then Amu or Yuna Yajima
Then Yuna Yajima.
Why is that?
Four.
It's too early.
It's totally fine... even for me.
You're wasting your time.
Okay, we're done.
Okay, now I'd like to decide who to expel.
First of all...
Yes, who do you think should be banned?
Yes, sir.
This one is done.
Four.
Then, who do you think should be banned, Mr. Winner?
One.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, then.Okay, then.
Four.
Oh, wow.
Eh, eh, eh, eh.
eh... eh... eh...
Huh. Blue, blue, blue, blue.
No, there's a deciding vote.
No, there's one person I'm pretty sure is a werewolf.
Okay, who do you think we should expel?
Raise your hand.
Worst. Worst.
Yuuki, Sasaki, Fujisaki, Yajima...
What? Why?
It's definitely going to be Yajima.
How about you, Nishii-san?
Raise your hand if you vote for Ms. Nishii
Yea
מססססס
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
And you, Mr. Kyushu? Yes, Kyushu.
Mr. Kyushu, maybe you'd like to open your hand.
Uh, yeah, that's right. It was Singh.
Yes, sir.
Okay, Shintoists, open your eyes slowly. Who would you like to consider today?
Fortune teller, please open your eyes.
Fortune teller, who would you like to divine?
Father, please open your eyes. Who will you protect today?
Okay, now it's time for everyone to open their eyes. Well, it's time, ladies and gentlemen, to open your eyes.
This time, the umbrella of death has protected us from the werewolves.
Oh, my God.
I didn't envision this.
A fortune teller with a place name got me into trouble in Yubapura.
It's a place name.
Well, well, well... Fujisaki's been there before.
He tried to kill Isshin.
But Inch was protecting Isshin.
That's funny.
The first time Isshin raised his hand to Yunami, I thought, "I'm going to kill him.
But if he kills Isshin, Yunami's a werewolf.
It'll be confirmed.
Good bye.
Let's begin.
Everyone, close your eyes.
Okay.
Okay, fortune-tellers, fortune-tellers, please open your eyes.
Then the knight, the knight, please open your eyes.
Then, mediums, please open your eyes.
Werewolf, Werewolf, please open your eyes.
Yes, first of all, let's start with the fortuneteller.
Yes, which one is the fortuneteller? I am.
No, I'm the fortune teller.
Then, you're over here already.
You're the werewolf type.
Yes, I'm suspicious.
It's me.It's me.
Eh, no. Look, I thought.
Eh, but this is a similar type. We're similar types.
At any rate, I'm different from these two.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, I'll put in Aisai Raku no Zessho.
Okay, Kyusho-kun.
Koheiku-kun.
Sasayaku.
One, two, three, four.
Uh, Iizuka-san.
Yes, sir.
More and more, more and more!
Wait, wait, wait!
Keep it coming, for sure!
Okay, now, Mr. Sasaki.
Sasaki-san.
Then Yajima-san. Yes.
It's okay!
Yes!
I'm Sasatakura this time, in the V Corner.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Well, I think I'm Miho Fujisaki.
First, the goal.
Who would you like to expel, werewolves?Who do the werewolves want to banish?
Who do the fortune tellers tell?
Who will the knight protect?
Okay, this time it's Sasagi who will be banished.
Wait, wait, wait.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I prefer Miyu.
Even if Haruma's a citizen.
Even if Haruma's a werewolf... if we dry Miyu once...
It'll reduce the number of werewolves.
We can definitely reduce the number of wolves by one.
I won't sell her, and I won't sell her if she's dead.
Wait a minute, you told her.
I told him off by mistake.
Then she was a werewolf.
Then expel Miyu.
And if you banish someone else...
Now we're down to two werewolves and a citizen.
If the werewolves eat her, it's the end of the game and we lose.
By the way, why do you say that?
You're like a fortune teller who's going to die.
Maybe...
No, you could die.
Why die?
Aihara, I think.
Kyushu-o, I think it's you.
Then, Koe...
No, me too...No, I think I'm over here too, Koe.
Okay, Mizubuka-san.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Then this one.
Seven.
Okay, then...
Mr. Fujisaki
I see...
Yajima-san. I see. I see.
The park will be banished.
A word? A good-looking guy?
Then who shall we expel?
Then, the fortune teller, who shall we tell?
The knights, who shall we protect?
Yes, and the medium, please open the ship.
It's Mr. Itch who will be banished today.
Uhhh...
Oh!
huh?
Ehhhh...
It's Shimin.
Woooo...
I'm probably going to lose this one.
I'm a true Shimin
Ehhh...
No way!Lie.
Then here, here, here.
Citizens
Why are you so suspicious?
Hey Shimin is
Shimin are
So, if it's the two of you, Benji, they'll be expelled.
What?
You can say as much as you want.
Well, then, like the moon, like the moon
Like the moon
Why not?
I thought your voice was definitely different.
The way she reacted...
I thought Haruma was probably a werewolf.
And maybe what Fujisaki said was true... and we're fortune tellers.
So he must have divined them.
So it's just the two of them
Seriously, Shirin.
It's just Shirin.
You're so mean, seriously!
I doubt Ru-chan
Why Shimin?
But now that we're here, it's the last turn.
I think it's better if Kishi leaves.
Kishi's leaving!
Okay, bye.Okay, then.
Yes, those who think Hara-kun is good
Yes, those who think Kichijo is good
Those who think Mizukawa-san is good
No, no.
People who think Mizuse-san should be expelled
Then, Mr. Yajima
Then, Ron.
Why?
Okay, Mizukawa.
Audience.
I'm a citizen.
Well, then, the citizen's team wins.
Yeah!
Roo-chan's acting is so weak.
No! I'm sure that's not Roo-chan's real laugh... and I'm going to catch it.
If it had been a close call, I would've done it... but the voice was so annoying...
If I had done Fujiki Mew, I would've won... but once he's gone, there's no one left to see.
Okay, first the fortune teller... the fortune teller... please open your eyes slowly
Knight, knight, please open your eyes.
Medium, please open your eyes.
Werewolf, Werewolf, please open your eyes slowly
Crow place
I've been doing this for a long time.
Boo-hoo!
That's it.
No booboo bar. Soon.
I can't go there. I can't go even though it's not a
me.
I don't know!
Hey!
Why?
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
Hey!
Yes, Mr. Sasaki.
Fujisaki
Mr. Fujisaki
Iitsuka-san, who I think you should report.
Go ahead.
No, it's hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, Mr. Sasaki.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes, yes...
Mr. Sasaki, I'm Baracy today.Mr. Sasaki, it's Baracy today.
Here you go.
Everybody, everybody.
Hey, 10 cards.
Yes, well, werewolves.
What happened to you?
Shall we banish them?
Yes, sir.
And who will the knights protect?
Mr. Yajima is to be banished today.
He's a monster.
We'll destroy the tour operators.
Fortune tellers?
There's a fortune teller.
We don't know. Maybe it's Aimi Sasaki.
Then it's Iichi, Kakune Kuro.
They're all citizens, so the fortuneteller had to appear.
So only two of them were the real fortunetellers.
If there is no fortuneteller, Iichi is the most suspicious.
Iichi is our knight.
I said it.
That's good! It's good!
Sep.
It's over!
Oh, no.Oh, no.
Wait a minute.
I didn't let the screen die.
Yes, Hara-kun.
Kyushu-kun.
Me, too, Kyusyu-kun.
Oh, me?
Yes, Koe.
Yes, sir.
Sato, Hara-kun.
Mr. Iizuka.
Mr. Iji
So, today, Mr. Fujisaki.
No turnabout?
What?
Then which of you werewolves would you like to expel?
Yes. Then, which of you fortune tellers would you like to divinate?
Who do you want to protect, the fortuneteller?
Fortune tellers never tire of long lists.
I never get tired of the long ones.
I don't care. I'm number one.
Then, fortune tellers, let me meet one.
Yes, please.
Fortune tellers, please let us meet them.
Yes, today, the recommended one is Mr. Ichiro.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Did you find this?Did you find this?
Because I'm a knight myself.
Is this your first time?
A knight can't protect his first time.
First time, apparently.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, yes, no, I'm a fortune teller.
I don't know.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, I don't know.
I just thought I'd come out when I found out who the werewolf was.
So you're going?
Ichi... Ichi... Ichi... you know, you held it up for me once, right?
I was sure you knew.
But I told you, I was a werewolf...
I was going to leave.
Oh, OK, OK.
Okay, I'll let you say it one more time.
I'm a medium.
Yes, I'm serious.
I read everyone's fortunes. They were citizens.
And by the way, I was a citizen on the first night I did my fortunetelling.
You win here.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
How much arm?
I'll take that arm. I'll take that arm.
I'm gonna do it again today.
Arm, arm, arm, arm. A lot of arms.
Once.
Sasaki, the werewolf.
Ha-ha-ha.
Well, if it doesn't end in rain...
If it doesn't end in rain, you cut off my cloth or feather horse, and you win.
Okay, I can do that.
Yay, yay, yay.
Divination's over.
Well, yes, spring.
You can do it.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes. - Yes.
No.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, there was one person who didn't know how to use the fortune teller.
No.
Yes!
Yes, the citizen team won!
Yay!
Ooh!
Oh!Oh!
That's great!
You're amazing, Miss.
You asked me to give you the werewolf floor.
I gave it to him because I thought he was in the mood to be with someone from that side or something.
I'm just thinking, you know, Madonnalee's with me.
I'm already in the mood.
By the way, I feel sorry for Miss who was hanged for nothing.
Everyone was going to hang her for Suzuki.
But I'm a fellow werewolf.
I felt it would be a little weird to hang him.
I decided to hang Fujisaki, who didn't say anything.
Then he gave me these two.
No, no, no. Miyu put Iizuka in.
When we parted on the first day...
That's why I thought Miyu might be suspicious.
I don't know what it is, but it's convenient for you.
Yeah, that's why.
I'm sorry about that.
That's great.
I was just trying it out for the first time.
I thought I was a knight and I just happened to make it.
I thought maybe I could do it again the next time, so I went to the knight and it wasn't the same.
It was hard.
I'm going to go study.
Next time you play wargames, please give me more appearances.
We had a lot of fun playing wargames.
It was a hospitality project language meeting.It was a hospitality project language meeting.